Hey, how are you?
>> Hey, how's it going?
>> I'm good. Tell me, what have you been
doing the last year?
>> Uh, a lot of rehab, a lot of PT, a lot
of training. Um, family time. Uh, a
little bit of travel. Um, mainly just
trying to get get right and get healthy.
>> Where'd you go?
>> Uh, like travel-wise.
>> Oh, yeah. But also, where do you tra
where do you train when you live all
that?
>> Um, I train out in Dallas in uh Frisco
um with a couple other O line guys. Um,
but I took a trip to Mexico. Um, got to
go back home, visit my family a couple
times. Yeah, that's about it.
>> What was life like away from the game
and did it change your perspective on
the game?
>> Um, it was very boring.
It was very boring. Um, but yeah,
definitely changed my perspective on the
game. I feel like I missed it more than
usual, you know, just being off and not
being out there and watching from home.
It was a little bit different.
>> Nick,
>> how's it going, Jedric? Uh what was
communicated to you from the Spars
coaching staff about the the left tackle
position and the situation that you're
entering into?
>> Um basically just opportunity. They they
wanted me to have here have me here on
the roster and uh they gave me another
chance to play and basically just
competition coming in and just trying to
prove what I can do and see where that
takes me.
>> Dion
welcome.
>> Sorry.
>> No, that's okay. That's okay. Welcome.
Um, it's nice to meet you. What do you
What do you think or why do you think I
guess that you're ready now to return to
the game and and what do you think
you're ready to jump into with this
Bears team?
>> Yeah, I feel like the last year that I
had off just really gave me the time I
needed to get healthy. Um, and I feel
way better in this position I am now
than I was a year ago. And um, yeah,
just excited to be a Bear and what this
team can do this year. I mean, I've seen
some great things over the past season.
So, just excited to bring my talents
here and um, just be an addition.
Zach,
>> hey. Going off of that, I was just gonna
ask you, what do you know about Ben
Johnson and and how much of the Bears
did you get to see last year? And what
what did you see?
>> Yeah. Um, I know that Ben's an energetic
coach. I know that he loves the big guys
up front, which is a positive for me.
Um, and yeah, the team did really good
things last year. I mean, they
completely turned around this program
and um, they were balling out and it was
really exciting to watch. So, uh,
excited to be here. Dan,
>> Dick, what was the the complexity of the
recovery with your knee that that
required so much time?
>> Um, so I didn't I injured a couple
ligaments. Um, but usually when people
like when they get fell on or something
in their knee, they mess up all their
ligaments and people can just go in and
repair it and they get healthy. Um, I
had minimal damage to my ligaments, it
was more of an alignment issue from
where I got fell on. Um, so they had to
actually, it wasn't my knee. They had to
go into my femur and do what was called
an osteotomy to kind of correct my
alignment. So my knee is healthy. It was
a matter of just letting that heal and
uh letting my letting my knee get
healthy. And um yeah, so it took it took
a little bit longer than just the
regular injury, but it's doing better
now.
>> Yeah.
When you've been at full strength in
your career, what do you describe as the
strengths of your game?
>> Um athletic. um very strong. Um I like
to get out in space and move around a
little bit. Um I think that my pass pro
is definitely a strong suit being able
to match with those athletic defensive
ends and their speed.
>> Um yeah,
>> Adam,
>> how difficult was it to maintain your
your your confidence as you kind of went
through your your rehab process? It
sounds long. obviously didn't play last
year, but how would you describe the
confidence in yourself now going
forward?
>> Yeah. Um I mean I definitely at first,
you know, once you get surgery, it's
you're you're down, you're injured,
you're obviously not yourself. Uh so you
just got to you just got to kind of gain
that back through working out, through
training, knowing that all the work that
you put in for the past year is going to
pay off. And um I've been working off to
get healthy. So I got think I got great
confidence in what I can do. Um just got
to fine-tune and make sure that my skill
set is ready to go. But, uh, I've put in
the work last year, so now it's just
time to, you know, have some fun again.
>> Last one, Pat.
>> Did you work out for them and and what
have the and what's been the process
like of convincing teams that that
you're good to go physically?
>> Yeah. Um, no, I did not work out when I
came to visit the Bears that last week,
I believe. Um, it was mostly just a lot
of medical meeting with the coaches, uh,
going through a little bit of film. Um,
but yeah, I'm healthy. I mean, I've been
training and uh been getting right. So,
yeah, I should be ready to go by by the
time I come back.
>> All right, last one. Dan
>> Jedrick, how much do you know about Joe
Tuni, who uh ideally you'll be lining up
next to if if you get that job?
>> Yeah, I know Joe Toney will be a future
Hall of Famer. I mean, he's a great guy
who's played this game for a long time
and um yeah, I'm excited to work with
him. I mean, his knowledge of the game
and his his veterans and how long he's
played, I mean, it'll be nothing but
positive for the room, I'm sure. So, me
being able to learn from him would do
nothing but help me.
>> Awesome. Thank you.